masoko.com 2019-04-14

# Privacy and Cookie Policy

We value the trust you place in Masoko.com. That's why we insist upon offering you the best service with highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy.   
Kindly go through following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, kindly review this policy from time to time. 

## 1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, etc.) from a customer when you set up an account with Masoko.com. As you browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, there are some activities that will require you to register. We do use your contact information to send you offers based on your previous orders, interests and searches on our website.

## 2\. Use of Demographic and Profile Data

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.  
As we continually improve on our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website. We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.   
We from time to time request you to complete some simple and optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like location, local government area, age, or income level or gender). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in--and to display content according to your preferences.

## Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Masoko.com places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. Masoko.com's cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information..

## 3\. Sharing of personal information

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to in an effort to detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. 

Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless opt-in is activated on your end.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary.

We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.  
In a case where Masoko.com and its affiliates plan to merge/partnership or acquisition occurs by another business entity, we will be required to share some or all of your personal information with. 

## 4\. Links to Other Sites

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Masoko.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.

## 5\. Security Precautions

Masoko.com has taken security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information. When a customer changes/accesses your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.

## 6\. Choice/Opt-Out

Masoko.com provides its users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.   
If you want to remove your contact information from all Masoko.com lists and newsletters, please unsubscribe from the email on the newsletter or click here to unsubscribe 

## 7\. Advertisements on Masoko.com

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

## 8\. Questions?

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: help@Masoko.com
